I see that Juna is sending me a message
me veo que me está mandando un mensaje
and she says Yuna against Saan at what
juna y me dice yuna contra saan en qué
time and I just said I don't know now I'm going to
momento y le acabo de No lo sé ya lo voy
watch it now Oh actually I closed the [ __ ]
a ver ahora Ay de hecho cerrado el [__]
Uncle Shuri video it's true it's true it's
vídeo del Tío shuri es verdad es verdad
true it's true it's true thank goodness he
es verdad es verdad es verdad menos mal
reminded me it was another guy what a
que me la recordado era otro cabrón qué
pain in the ass it was another one it was another one
putada me era otra era otra
here the king of C no [ __ ] [ __ ] I didn't
aquí el rey del C no [__] [__] que no
know I didn't remember this topic
lo sabía que no me acordaba de este tema
and it's true I have it in the title I have please Juna made
y es verdad lo tengo puesto en el título
a billion
please juna se marcó un billin Por
Why why
qué por
[Music]
[Música]
Mm from the message that I sent you I don't understand it I think that she should upload it no I'm
Mm por el mensaje que te envío no lo
not going to upload it tell these people that you upload it and tell us can you imagine what school Hey it's ...
mucho lo que pasa es que no pongo nada
a clar that everything I
no sé cuando e yo una clar que todo lo
say is a hint eh Everything I
que digo es una indirecta eh Todo lo que
do is a hint yes if I talk about
hago es una indirecta si si hablo de
aliens in a in a tweet and I say Put the
aliens en un en un tweet y pongo Pon la
truth before your eyes so that
verdad delante de tus ojos para que
no one can see it is a hint it is not about
nadie pueda verla es una indirecta no es
aliens it is a hint everything is
de aliens es una indirecta todo es
Indira everything is wrong despite all
Indira todo está mal a pesar de todo
this says that she is happy for the team and
esto dice que se alegra por el equipo y
that the decisions of people are of
que las decisiones de personas son de
people then Of course on social networks
persona entonces Claro en redes sociales
and all that I do not say anything but
y todo eso no digo nada pero
evidently yes I know that they are in the
evidentemente sí que sé que están en la
final for And yes I know that I am
final for Y sí que sé que me alegro
very happy for them and I hope the girls
muchísimo por ellos y ojalá las chicas
eh Also reach to their final for
eh También lleguen a a a su final for
later and I hope they finally win eh what they did
más adelante y ojalá ganen por fin eh lo
not win being with me because I
que no ganaron estando conmigo porque yo
eh you can think what you can think I
eh podéis pensar lo que podéis pensar ni
am not angry nor do I hold grudges or
estoy enfadada ni guardo rencores ni
obviously anything like that and one thing
evidentemente nada de eso y una cosa
is also the people and another thing is
también son las personas y otra cosa es
the team so okay let's see I understand
el equipo entonces vale a ver entiendo
at first I was going to tell you [ __ ]
al principio iba a deciros [__]
too much diplomacy it seems to me this no
demasiado diplomacia me parece esto no
But of course I understand that she is
Pero claro entiendo que está haciendo
referring to that one thing is
referencia a que una cosa es
eh one thing  It's
eh una cosa es
gref no and another
gref no y otra
HM of course the team not players
HM claro el equipo no jugadores
[Music]
[Música]
fans for me personally it's sans it's been
afición yo personalmente es sans ha sido
my team and since it's been my team I don't let my
mi equipo y como ha sido mi equipo yo no
feelings go away like it's
se me van los sentimientos de en plan es
my team overnight pum pum pum it does
mi equipo de la noche a la mañana pum
n't go away so what to say is
pum pum no se me va entonces qui decir
I'm happy for the triumphs and I'm
yo me alegro por los triunfos y me
happy for the achievements, I mean it's that it
alegro por los logros o sea es que me me
gives me I mean I'm not a person yes I am a
da O sea no soy una persona sí soy una
resentful person but in this case
persona rencorosa pero en este caso no
I'm not resentful because I understand I mean I don't
soy rencorosa porque entiendo O sea no
feel guilty about anything You know
me siento culpable De nada Sabes
then I don't care I mean you've made
entonces me da igual o sea tú has tomado
a decision and that's it you know it doesn't
una decisión y ya está sabes no
mean that I have to be bad with the team
significa que yo con el equipo tenga que
or with anyone I have to be
estar mal ni con nadie tengo que estar
bad with I'm fine On the other hand I would say
mal yo estoy bien Por otra parte diría
that I don't hold any kind of grudge No I don't hold any
que no guarda ningún tipo de rencor No
grudge in this in this aspect
no tengo rencor en este en este aspecto
It's that I think the following each one of us
Es que yo pienso lo siguiente cada uno
are owners of our own
somos dueños de nuestras propias
decisions, For example if
decisiones yo Por ejemplo si hubiera
I had been the owner of a soccer team
sido yo la dueña de un equipo de fútbol
something happens to me with a person I decide
me pasa x cosa con una persona yo decido
No yes eh I try to fix yes no I don't know
No si eh intento arreglar si no no sé
how many how serious something is for
cuántos qué gravedad tiene x cosa para
me  If I say look, for me it's a lot
mí si digo Mira es que para mí es mucho
or for me it's less, I don't know, I make the
o para mí es menos no sé tomo la
decision because I'm the owner, no, so
decisión porque soy la dueña no entonces
whoever the owner is can make whatever
m quien sea el dueño pues puede tomar la
decision they want and obviously I've
decisión que quiera y evidentemente pues
stayed the same. I mean,
me he quedado igual O sea quiero decir
I've stayed the same, I'm simply not going to
me quedó igual simplemente que no voy a
go to the girls' games or be
ir a los partidos de las chicas ni seré
president, but I'm the same, I mean, I don't know
presidenta pero estoy igual o sea no sé
if I'm the same, no, it doesn't affect me
si soy igual no me no me repercute a
negatively in my life. You know, like,
nivel negativo en mi vida Sabes en plan
saying, It's not that now I'm going to earn
de decir No es que ahora voy a ganar
less, it's not that I'm the same. So that's why I
menos no es que estoy igual Entonces
don't hold a grudge
pues por eso no guardo renc
because, let's see, let's see, let's see, there's
porque muy a ver a ver a ver a ver aquí
a movement here, okay. And this
hay una movidad vale Y esto
is my personal opinion, uh,
es mi opinión personal eh
my personal opinion, my personal
mi opinión personal mi opinión personal
opinion, let's leave it as a
vamos a dejarlo en opinión
personal opinion. Let's see, let's
personal A ver a ver a
see, of course, here what I see,
ver claro yo aquí lo que lo que veo yo
here what I see is that although
aquí lo que veo es que aunque van
the days go by and the issue is being
pasando los días y el tema se va
left behind. It's that this, of course. It's that what
quedando atrás Es que esto claro Es que
Yuna has done, for me, is a
esto que ha hecho yuna para mí es un
very big mistake when
error muy grande cuando a ti te pasa
something as big as what happened happens to you, I
algo tan gordo como lo que pasó hace ya
think it was three weeks ago, or around
creo que sea tres semanas o por ahí no
three or four. I don't know, okay,
tres o cuatro No lo sé vale
if you  you
m si tú te lo
swallow it okay And you have your version but
tragas vale Y tú tienes tu versión pero
you swallow it for whatever reason out of fear
tú te lo tragas por lo que sea por miedo
for example no for whatever
por ejemplo no por lo que sea
no in the end that's what it is inside here if you
no al final eso aquí dentro si tú te lo
leave it in your chest It creates a
dejas en el pecho Te va creando aquí un
little tumor here like I was saying with another
tumorcillo como yo decía con otro
colleague No that's what it is inside here it keeps you quiet it keeps you quiet it
compañero No eso aquí dentro te calla te
creates a little
calla te calla te crea Aquí un
tumor that you have here that you have to
tumorcillo que lo tienes que eso hay que
get it out then of course it keeps coming out it goes on it goes
sacarlo entonces claro va sacando va va
like
va como
caving in and caving in caving in in the
capoteando y capoteando capoteando al
end when it explodes
final cuando explote ya no le va a
nobody will be interested or it will be too late or
interesar a nadie o ya va a ser tarde o
the other one will have it you know
ya el otro lo va a tener sabes
eh So what can I tell you? Well here he just said that he doesn't care that they
eh Entonces qué te digo Pues aquí acaba
fired him because he earns the
echado porque cobra lo
same okay or basically nobody has
mismo vale o sea básicamente nadie te ha
written down your intentions no no it's that
anotado tus intenciones no no es que
let's see what he just said here
vamos a ver que te acaba de soltar aquí
that they didn't pay him they
que no le pagaban
rehearse no me it doesn't affect me
ensayan no me no me repercute a nivel
negatively in my life You know like
negativo en mi vida Sabes en plan de
saying No it's that now I'm going to earn less it's
decir No es que ahora voy a ganar menos
not that I'm the same then well eh That's why I
no es que estoy igual entonces pues eh
don't hold a grudge because I'm the
Por eso no guardo rencor porque estoy
same with less responsibilities what is it for that  It's that they did
igual con menos responsabilidades para
n't pay him,
que está que está que que no le pagaban
let's say he's earning the
vamos que está ganando lo
same as he was, he's earning the
mismo que estaba que está ganando lo
same but they don't
mismo pero que no le
pay him, it was already known, Juan said what
pagan ya se sabía lo dijo Juan qué
Juan, I personally think that he
Juan yo personalmente opino que se
should let out his anger, right
debería desahogar verdad
guys, I'm personally going to
chavales yo personalmente se lo voy a
tell him wait
decir espera
[Laughs] he
[Risas]
gained more free time he lost views no no I
ganó más tiempo libre perdió views no no
mean he's the same he's not the same no yes it's not going to be it's not
O sea está igual
going to be it's also going to comment that being
va a ser también comentar de que estar
out of s doesn't bring him any problems since he would
fuera de s no le trae ningún problema ya
n't charge for it and also he would be
que no cobraría por ello y además se
freed from responsibilities without more and I'm
quitaría responsabilidades sin más y me
happy for the triumphs Of course I'm
alegro por los triunfos Claro que me
glad that Yuna comes in I see that he
alegro que entre yuna Yo veo que se
should let out his anger But well if he doesn't
debería desahogar Pero bueno si no
want to but it's going to go sando you know what's going to
quiere pero va ir sando sabéis lo que va
happen that's going to go sando this type of
a pasar que va ir sando este tipo de
chick this type of chick all the
pollita este tipo de pollita todo el
time all the time in the end whether he wants to or not he's
tiempo todo el tiempo al final quiera
looted with a percentage of his
que no saqueado con un porcentaje de su
image stained by the [ __ ] that
imagen manchada por la [__] que le
gref threw at him you know eh eh eh I don't hold a
tiró gref sabes eh eh eh No guardo
grudge even with the cherry Yes more
rencor ni con la cerecita Sí más
freedom I have less responsibilities and I
libertad tengo menos responsabilidades y
earn the same So eh losing I have
gano lo mismo Así que eh perder he
lost  Well the only thing I've lost is
perdido pues lo único que he perdido es
being with the girls that I
el estar con las chicas que me gustaba
really liked and that project Well I liked it I
mucho y y el el el proyecto ese Pues que
like the team I like it I was
a mí me gustaba me gusta el equipo me
excited about it And such But that's the
gusta me hacía ilusión Y tal Pero es lo
only thing I would conclude with juna if they
único con esto concluiría juna si te
offered you another team Well if they
ofrecieran otro equipo Pues si me
offered me another team we would have to
ofrecieran otro equipo habría que
talk about it because right now I'm like
hablarlo porque yo ahora mismo Estoy en
Cool clar I'm very good because I've taken
plan Guay clar Yo estoy muy bien porque
off a responsibility that I
me he quitado una responsabilidad que
had Well in the end it's a
tenía que Bueno al final es una
big responsibility so I've taken
responsabilidad grande entonces me he
off that responsibility I focus on
quitado esa responsabilidad me centro en
my things which That's good for me
mis cosas lo cual Eso es bueno para mí
but it's true that maybe
pero sí que es verdad que a lo mejor
in X months I'll have missed it let's
dentro de X meses lo he hecho de menos a
see I've missed the team and
ver yo he hecho de menos al equipo y
all that what happens is that the quein
todo eso lo que pasa es que la quein
is stopped But who's to say that
está parada Pero quién me dice que
when the Queens starts I'm not going to
cuando empiece la Queens no lo voy a
miss it we would have to talk about it and we would have to
echar de menos habría que hablarlo y
talk about conditions that in the
habría que hablar condiciones que en el
past case Well I'm not going to say anything but we
pasado bueno no voy a decir nada pero
would have to talk about other conditions that
habría que hablar otras condiciones que
other things is that in the end man this
otras cosas es que al final tío esto te
creates you Here inside I mean eh I don't know if you
crea Aquí dentro o sea eh yo no sé si lo
're noticing it okay or whatever But
estáis notando ustedes vale o sea Pero
in the end this creates you Here inside it
al final te esto te crea Aquí dentro te
creates you  In here something creates
crea Aquí dentro una cosa te crea una
something it creates something for you that well that's it
cosa te crea una cosa que bueno ya está
because in the end you'll leave it halfway and you'll
pues al final lo dejarás a media y te
regret not letting it go over time
arrepentirá con el tiempo de no soltarlo
you know what I'm telling you what I'm telling you each
sabes lo que te digo qué Te digo cada
one does what they want okay gref put her as an
uno c lo que quiera vale gref la puso de
intern no but let's see here she's
becaria no pero a ver aquí te está
telling you more or less like she didn't
diciendo ya más o menos como que no
have good ones but it's not like it's about
tenía unas buenas pero no es que se
conditions that she didn't even have a
trate de condiciones que ni siquiera
contract or he paid her or
tenía contrato ni le pagaba ni
anything I can see her bad face I think she
nada Yo le noto mala cara creo que
needs to let it out me it's just that I do
necesita soltarlo yo yo es que estas
n't care about these things you know Or rather it's
cosas no me las queo sabes O sea que
where it is God will say Or rather if
está por donde está Dios dirá O sea si
you have your talent and you have your things
tú tienes tu talento y tienes tus cosas
and you have t moves no And you have gotten to
y tienes t movidas no Y tú has llegado a
where you have gotten on your own without King le and
donde has llegado tú sola sin King le y
without King long
sin King long
Well tell the
Pues cuenta la
truth you know tell the truth and that's it [ __ ] up
verdad sabes cuenta la verdad y ya está
whoever wants to
que den por culo a to el que te quiera
open the door for you well lock it
haer la puerta pues que le eche la llave
and don't open it tomorrow you understand If it's anything
y no la abra mañana me entiendes Si es
else no
que otra cosa no
anyway T div
fin T div